翻译 牙牙 右翼部鸣明 校对 Linn Husky 草草
时间轴 SG 填字 右翼部鸣明Matisse
资源搬运 yoyo 文本处理 谷子 yoyo
史蒂文 我们可能要离开一段时间
All right, we may be a while.
可是...紫晶！
But --Amethyst!
啥事？我忙着呢ˊ_>ˋ
What? I'm busy.
紫晶，保持警惕
Amethyst,hold down the fort.
知道啦～长官
Aye, aye, Captain.
我负责期间绝不会有任何意外
No surprises while I'm on duty.
啥！
Wha--!
萨普莱斯!我早到啦～
Surprise! I'm early!
我刚想告诉你 康妮约好了在今天进行剑术训练的
I was trying to tell you Connie has sword training today.
OMG 我全忘了！
Oh! I completely forgot.
非常抱歉 康妮
I'm so sorry, Connie.
噗嗤 ，“珍”不靠谱
Very irresponsible, Pearl.
哼
Mnh.
你们是要去找铁石英吗？
Is this because of Jasper?
要调头去北方吗？
Are you headed back north?
她依然在四处活动
She's on the move.
我们不能任由
We can't have her just out there,
她到处刷怪！
attacking random monsters for whatever reason.
当然了！注意安全喔
Of course. Be safe.
那可是我的专属台词
That's my line.
紫晶？-知道啦
Amethyst? Got it.
我们下周再进行训练吧
We'll train next week
只要铁石英不再让我们头疼
without Jasper hanging over our heads.
这是最理想的了
Best-case scenario.
你们这些幸运的家伙，逃过了训练日！
Lucky break for you guys --You get the training day off.
所以 接下来你们想干啥？
So, what do you want to do?
噢？哈？
Oh? Huh?
嘿 你开挂！
Hey, no fair.
嘿嘿 紫晶 你看见那招了吗？
Hey, Amethyst, did you see that?
紫晶？
Amethyst?
咋了？
'Sup?
你有在看我们训练吗？
Are you even watching?
当然咯 不然你觉得我在干嘛
Sure. What's it look like?
我觉得你没在看
Like you're not watching.
唔 尊讨厌
Oh, all right.
被你逮到了
You got me.
现在好多了吧～
Is that better?
噫！-好恶
Ew! Gross. Ew! Gross.
但是-唔 确实好多了
But, yeah, that's better.
来吧康妮  我们从头再来一遍
Come on, Connie. Let's take it from the top.
好的！
Okay!
你看到了吗？
Did you see  that?
噢 那！
Excellent! Amazing!
珍是极好的
Pearl-fect.
没有啦/w\
Ohh. I don't know. Not really.
我的站姿完全是错的-力度也不够！
My stance is all wrong, and my grip is a little soft.
你为什么要纠结于这些小事？
What are you worried about that little stuff for?
在战场上 这些根本无关紧要
It's not gonna matter in a real fight.
但这确实很重要
It does, though.
我毁掉了我第一次魔法任务
I blew it on my first real magical mission.
我直面那只宝石怪兽 却手足无措
I was face-to-face with a monster, and I froze.
我之前用心一点训练的话 那次任务就不会失败了
Maybe if I'd trained a little harder, I could have handled it.
在我看来 你就是想的太多了
Sounds to me like you're too in your own head.
真正战斗的时候-每一秒都是难以预测的
In a fight, you never know what's gonna happen.
你只有临场发挥
You just got to go with it.
不然你怎么能为那些
How can you get ready when you don't even know
你根本不知道的事做准备？what you're getting ready for, huh?
没错 根本没有时间准备
Yeah, you can't be ready.
你唯一需要做的事情 就是 放～轻～松～
What you got to be is loose.
我也想放轻松！
I want to be loose!
然后你就可以跟着感觉走了！
Then you got to go with the flow.
战斗靠的就是肚子深处的那种感觉！！
Fighting's all about that feeling deep in your guts.
你的肚肚感觉怎么样？
What do your guts feel like?!
饿！
Hungry.
我也一样
Mine, too.
来点零食！来点零食！
Snack break. Snack break.
唔 我们的训练需要进食来补充能量
Well, we do need energy to practice.
来点零食！来点零食！来点零食！
Snack break! Snack break!Snack break! Snack break!
谁要吃甜甜圈？
Who wants doughnuts?
我要我要！也许一个就够了
I do! Maybe just one!
OK 我请客
Great.It's on me.
像一个汉堡
♪ Like a burger ♪
马上就来！
Be right there!
欢迎光临大甜甜圈！想来点什-----哈？
Welcome to the Big Donut. How can I hel-- Wha-- Huh?
呦～甜甜圈女孩儿
Hey, donut girl.
是我 甜甜圈男孩
It's me, Donut Boy.
介意我拿几个酥脆甜甜圈吗？
You mind if I grab a couple of crullers?
拿了也没关系，我就在这工作呢！
It's cool.I totally work here.
什么情况.....
What the...
莎蒂 抱歉
Sorry, Sadie.
紫晶又用
It's just Amethyst bein' Amethyst
她的一贯作风捣乱了
by not...bein' Amethyst.
没关系的 史蒂文
Eh, it's no problem, Steven.
只是一点甜甜圈罢了
It's just a couple of donuts.
！(◎_◎;)好吧 这可是个大问题
Okay,maybe it's a problem.
来呀
Come on!
快来吧
我没有带泳衣啦
I didn't bring a swimsuit!
在战斗的热潮中
In the heat of battle,
你是不会有什么泳衣的 康妮
you're not gonna have a swimsuit, Connie.
我的老天 你说的太对了
By Jove, I guess you're right.
我从来不记得哪天我有这么开心过
I don't think I've ever had this much fun in one day.
我们应该经常找紫晶玩
We should spend more time with Amethyst.
她最棒了
She's the best!
你才最棒
You're  the best.
不不不 你才最棒
Nuh-uh, you're the best.
呃 我也还记得你呢 哥们儿
Uhhh... I remember you, too, buddy.
紫晶 你刚才太给力了
Amethyst, that was amazing!
哇 你没事儿吧
Whoa! Are you okay?
赢得不太漂亮 不过无所谓啦
Not a pretty win, but I'll take it.
这就是那天我们在雪地里打过的怪兽
That was the monster we fought in the snow.
起码…看上去是的
At least, it looked like it was.
我觉得你没认错
I think you'd remember a face like that.
呃 当初是有两只
Well, there were two of them.
两只
Two of them?
玫瑰
Rose.
铁石英
Jasper!
找到你真是令人喜悦啊
Glad I found you.
我已经决定要建立我自己的军队了
I've decided to build my own army.
你的又在哪
Where's the rest of yours?
她们现在不在这儿
They're not here right now!
嘘
Shh!
那么就只有你们了
So, it's just you lot?
那又如何
Doesn't matter.
我自己照样可以抽得你满地滚
I'm gonna whip your butt all by myself!
铁石英交给我 你们去搞定那玩意
I got Jasper. You guys handle that dope.
好了 这是我们第二次的机会
Okay, we get a second chance at this.
我们只需要团结一致
Just stay together.
我是来和玫瑰决斗的 而非你这侏儒
I came here to fight Rose, not some runt!
你认为你现在就只能不断
You think you can just keep showing up
冒出来寻衅打架 哈
and picking fights with us?! Ha!
你就不能去享受下生活吗
Why don't you get a life?!
战斗就是我生活的全部
Fighting is my life!
我为此而生
It's what I was made for.
你也一样 侏儒
It's what you were made for too, runt.
那又怎样 我的生活可是无比丰富多彩
So? I've got other stuff goin' on.
是因为你觉得你自己已经是个失败者了吗
It is because you know you're already a failure?
你压根没尽力
You're not even trying.
是因为你觉得自己已经是个失败者了吗
Is it because you know you're already a failure?
你和我一样 都是石英战士
You're a Quartz Soldier, just like me.
但是你跟我一点都不像 不是吗
But you're not like me, are you?
你太渺小了
You're small!
紫晶
Amethyst?!
你已经渴望一支军队渴望到了
Are you that desperate for troops, Rose,
连这种残废都要留着的地步吗 玫瑰
that you keep a defect like this?!
玫瑰说了…这样的我…是最完美的
Rose said...I'm perfect... the way I am.
那她的眼光可有够低的
Then she had low standards.
你…本可以成为与我一样的存在
You...could have been me!
但是看看现在的你算什么东西
And what are you instead?
紫晶
Amethyst!
不过是个笑话而已
Just a joke.
快来
Come on!
是时候结束这场闹剧了
Time to get rid of this embarrassment.
你们融合了？！
You fused?!
哇
Whoa!
我-我融合了
I-I did.
你们水晶宝石居然还跟人类融合
You Crystal Gems would even fuse with a human?!
我不想再听你的一句废话
I don't want to hear anything you say
除非你准备道歉
unless it's, "Sorry."
你给我回来 败家玩意
Oh, no, you don't.
在这等着 我会保护你的
Wait here. I'll protect you.
一对一 我喜欢
Head-to-head, just like I like it.
准备好了就尽管上吧
Ready when you are.
史蒂文 康妮 我回来了
Steven, Connie, I'm back!
呃 一切都会没事
--Uh, everything's gonna be fi--
融合 融合
Fusion! Fusion!
又特么是融合
It's always fusion!
你准备好道歉了没
Are you ready to apologize?
这只是热身
This was just a warm-up.
我还会回来的 玫瑰
Get ready for next time, Rose.
俺们铁石英从来不会放弃
Jaspers don't give up!
谁也阻止不了俺们铁石英…得到俺们想要的东西
Jaspers keep going... until we get what we want.
我想她现在可算是住海里了
Hmm. I guess she lives in the ocean now.
你们…赢了
You guys...won?
-你回来了 -你没事
You're back! You're okay!
谢天谢地
Thank goodness!
呃 谢谢了伙计们
Uh, thank you,guys.
你刚才看见我们了吗 就真的像你说的
--Did you see us? It was just like you said --
你陷入麻烦 我们只要战斗就行了
you were in trouble, and we just had to fight!
我们所知的一切就会自动拼凑在一起
Everything we knew just came together.
我们融合了
We fused!
然后我们就赢了
We won!
我等不及要告诉其他人了！
I can't wait to tell the others!
噢 太好了
Oh, good.
你们根本不需要我
You didn't need me at all.